

SHAIK RASHIQ SALEEM

SENIOR QUALITY ASSURANCE ENGINEER

+91- 9441323306

1–1–219, Gopi Vihar street, Pulivendula, Kadapa, AP

mail2.rashiq@gmail.com https://www.rashiqsahik.im

in LinkedIn: shaik rashiq saleem

I'm a software test engineer with over 6+ years of experience working in the tech industry, providing functional and automation testing to deliver faster and more reliable defect free applications which enhances the user experience and increase customer satisfaction.

AREAS OF EXPERTISE

- Designing an Automation framework from scratch using JavaScript, WebdriverlO and Nodejs
- Understanding the business requirements and application design, preparing test cases, test plan and documenting the requirements and results
- Experience in API testing using postman

SKILLS

- Languages Javascript, JAVA
- Automation Tools and Frameworks –
 WebdriverIO, Protractor, Selenium, Cucmber
 TestNG
- API Testing Tool Postmar
- CL & CD Tools Jenkins
- Version Controls -Git, Bitbucket, Sourcetree
- Defect Tracking Jira, HP-ALN
- Database Monogdb and SQL
- OS Windows and Linux
- Other Tools and Technologies Docker, HTML & CSS, Nodejs, Expressis

EDUCATION

ELECTRICAL AND ELECTRONICS ENGINEERING

- Bachelor of Technology from JNTUA 2011-2015
- CGPA-77.45%

PROFESSIONAL HISTORY

SENIOR MEMBER TECHINCAL

ADP | APRIL2020 - PRESENT

- Working in Doccloud project which manages the documents of all the clients of ADP.
- SME of Docceloud
- Gather the functional requirements, test and report defects and sign off a release.
- Automate the test cases and maintain the tramework using javascript, webdriverio, nodejs, cucumber

QA ENGINEER

LEGATO | AUGUST 2019 - APRIL 2020

- Worked on Healthcare and Insurance domain project
- Writing Test Scenarios, Test Case documentation and test data collection for manual testing.
- Automation of desktop applications using Winnium

SYSTEM ENGINEER

TCS | JANUARY 2016 - AUGUST 2019

- Worked on two different projects, Rogers from Telecom and Davita Healthcare domain
- Analyzina Functional requirements
- Functional and Regression Testing
- Prepration and execution of testscripts using Java,